A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Budget Histories, Series 7 FA810
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Budget Histories, Series 7
1909-1963
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA810
12 Cubic Feet 10 record storage containers.
10 record storage cartons.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 210-7
Conditions Governing Access note
Restricted from scholarly research pending further processing. Personnel-related material closed.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids
FA811 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Henry James Subject Files, Series 1.
FA808 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Correspondence, Series 2.
FA137 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3.
FA809 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Annual Reports, Series 4.
Cell and biomolecular sciences; Vivisection; Biology -- Research; Medical research; Life sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Biochemistry; Hospitals; Prevention and health; Medical technology; Operations management; Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- Budget Histories, 1909-1963; 7; 10 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes primarily drafts of budget proposals, clippings, memoranda, notes, salary histories, and salary spreadsheets used in preparation of the RIMR budgets.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged primarily in chronological order.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted from scholarly research pending further processing. Personnel-related material closed.
  - Budget histories, 1909-1922 (Box 1)
    - War Demonstration Hospital budgets, 1918-1919 (Box 1)
  - Budget histories, 1922-1929 (Box 2)
  - Budget histories, 1929-1936 (Box 3)
  - Budget histories, 1936-1942 (Box 4)
  - Budget histories, 1942-1949 (Box 5)
  - Budget histories, 1949-1957 (Box 6)
  - Budget histories, 1956-1958 (Box 7)
  - Budget histories, 1958-1960 (Box 8)
  - Budget histories, 1960-1962 (Box 9)
  - Budget histories, 1962-1963 (Box 10)